The film you are about to see is a work of fiction
And yet it is closely based on ancient legends and folk tales
The film deal with evil powers , ghosts , spirits , witches , black magic
None of which have any place in our modern world
We advise you to watch this film as entertainment only
lt is pure fiction and should be treated as such
Behold Mahakal !
The master of all who seek evil in this world
Forsaking the virtuous path , they choose the path of evil
They forsake God
and seek succour with the Devil
Behold Nakita !
Her lustful body infused with black magic
To fulfil her evil desires she wanders the black nights of death
searching for the light of life
Behold Satan 's slave !
A wizard who practices black magic
to ruin innocent lives and bring destruction
Hail Mahakal !
Let go of me !
Please ... Let me go !
Let me go !
Who are you ?
Who are you ! ?
What are you doing ?
Why have you brought me here ?
What do you want ?
Listen to me ...
This night , Nakita will quench her thirst by drinking your warm blood
No ! No ! . ..
Hail Mahakal !
No ! No !
They 've found a dead body
A dead body ?
Who is it ?
It 's a stranger , Thakur sir
We found four of them
ln the dark forest
Hanging from the trees or floating in the lake
This has been going on for many years
But who kills them ?
A woman
She meets travellers at night , far from the village
She seduces them with her body and leads them astray
Then she sucks all the blood from them
But these are just old wives ' tales
We don 't believe in ghosts and witches today
You should believe , sir . Witches exist
- But who 's ever seen one ? - l have , sir
A few years back , I was returning here from the city
I lost my way and wandered into the lonely forest
There I saw a beautiful girl lurking behind the trees
But , before my eyes , she turned into a bat . ..
... and she flew onto my face
And she clawed at my flesh
I 've seen death with my own eyes , Thakur sir
lf this story is true . ..
If a witch haunts that lonely place , then I should be able to find her
You want to find her ? Have you gone crazy ?
If not me , then at least think about your daughter
God forbid something happens to you
Nothing will happen to me , Preeti
Don 't get so worried
But why put yourself in such danger ?
It 's our duty to serve and to protect those weaker than us
What my brother Sameer says is true
lt 's the only way to quash their fears
Here
Let God protect you !
It looks like the villagers were right about this witch
- Where are you headed ? - To where this road leads
But there 's nothing there , only the dark forest
But my house is in that dark forest
Do you live all alone here , in this big house ?
If you want you can stay here with me tonight
This is a fine room
lt 's my bedroom
I like your bedroom very much
I 'll quench this desire not with alcohol but with water
Looks like you 're getting ready to slay me
You 're a killer , I 'm a killer . Let 's waste no more time
Get out of those clothes and come here
I want to explore every inch of you
You 're clinging to me as a snake clings to the sandalwood tree
Your skin is just like a serpent 's skin
A poisonous serpent
Be careful
This serpent might bite
Witch !
Poisonous serpent !
I knew that you were no human , but a witch
Kill her !
Hail Mahakal !
Nakita
They destroyed your body
But your spirit lives on
I 'll find you a new body
The body of Thakur Mahindra Pratap 's daughter
Sameer , I don 't know why , but I feel uneasy about this trip
Stay here today
I know you care about me , but you have no need to worry
Daddy , vacation finished 4 days ago
lf l don 't go back to school my friends will worry
You worry more about friends than about work
Brother , your daughter is starting to grow up
I 'll take Jasmin to school and return tomorrow
After all Massouri is not far
Why have we stopped , uncle ?
I 'll check it out
The engine 's over heated
Jasmin , I 'm going to find some water
You stay here . All right ?
Hail Mahakal !
Jasmin
You can never kill me
What 's going on ?
Who are you ... ?
What do you want ?
Who could that be so late at night ?
Jasmin , what happened ?
- Where is your uncle ? - Who are you ?
There was a terrible storm , Thakur sir
There was a bad accident
I found this child alone in the forest
I saved her from a certain death
- Where 's Sameer ? - l 'm sorry , sir
i 'm afraid he 's dead
His body was washed away in the flood
No ...
- Ramu , take care of Jasmin . - Yes , sir
Now may I leave , Thakur sir
Baba , you saved Jasmin 's life
I want you to look after her
Please , I insist
lf this is your wish , then I shall live here
My shadow will follow your child at all times
You 're imagining it
No I 'm not , it 's true
Since Jasmin was found in the forest she 's completely changed
I saw it with my own eyes
God knows who she talks to when she 's alone
Children play with dolls
But Jasmin buries her dolls in the ground for fun
What 's up with you ?
You can 't believe all this nonsense
You must trust me , brother
Jasmin needs spiritual help
Take her to a priest or wise man
I fear she might be possessed
By an evil spirit
Jasmin , go to bed now
Today you shall die
Brother ... !
Brother , open the door ! Brother , open the door !
Open the door ! She 'll kill me
Open the door !
Daughter-in-law ! What happened ?
Open the door , daughter-in-law !
- Open the door , brother ! - Open the door !
She 'll kill me ! She 'll kill me !
Who will kill you ! What 's going on ?
- Open the door ! - Open the door !
Daughter-in-law !
What happened , daughter-in-law ?
- My child . - Mummy ... mummy
I won 't let Sahila stay in this cursed house
I 'll send her to Mumbai
To her granny 's place
You 're very happy , Thakur sir
Baba , the news is good . Sahila came first in her college exams
That is indeed good news
I 'll telegram her today to visit us for the vacation
Granny ! Granny ! A telegram from uncle !
He wants me to visit them at Chandan village
I 'm granny 's nephew . Granny is making burgers for me
But why are you wearing this sari ?
I 'll explain . .. You see , I 'm writing a horror story
The hero of this story turns into a woman at midnight
idiot !
He 's bone idle and does nothing but eat
Granny !
Always making up horror stories
- What rubbish ! - Shut up !
Granny , I 'm going to stay with uncle
Good . But can you take this fool with you too
Or he 'll drive me crazy with his stories
I 'll go with her on one condition
What ?
That you do a break dance in my film
I 'll give you break dance !
The Witch Queen !
Bandit Queen ! Help me !
Have you saved any milk for me ?
Or did you give it all to this creature ?
I 've got the vegetables . I 'll take them inside
You 're in a hurry , my sweet . How about a cup of tea ?
Get lost ! I 'm not your servant !
Why are you so angry ? is the Thakur at home ?
He 's still at the factory
So nobody 's at home ?
Jasmin is here . She 's upstairs taking a bath
A bath . ..
Beloved ... my beloved ...
From that world to this world , I came to search for you
Beloved .. my beloved
Beloved .. where are you ?
Where are you ? Where are you ? Where are you ?
To make your dream come true ...
I 've got the darkest of tresses
To make your dream come true
Beloved ... where are you ?
Where are you ? Where are you ? Where are you ?
You ?
What are you doing here ?
I 've got the vegetables . .. And fruits
Then take them to the kitchen
This isn 't the kitchen , is it ?
Papa is too soft on him ! Dirty old perv !
Zimbaru !
Thakur Mahindra Pratap 's niece has already left for Chandan village
But she 'll not reach the house
Abduct her on the way
What happened ? Where am I ?
- The Stones sang a song ? - The road 's blocked
Unblocking roads is my specialty
Hail Lord Hanuman
I don 't know my own strength
It looks like it was raining rocks
I 'll sort this out
Hurry up
Was that my pants ?
What was that noise ?
You often hear strange noises in the jungle
What harm have I ever done to you ? Eh ... ?
Help me !
Hey ! You ! Hey , big guy ! Tarzan ... !
What are you doing up there ?
That big guy made me climb the tree !
Help me !
I 'm here ! In the old graveyard !
- Who 's that ? - My leading lady
That crazy guy is after her Go there quickly , or else ...
Who are you ?
I 'm a lady in distress . I need help
I 've come to help you
A great big ugly fat guy is after me . I 'm afraid of what he might do
Please save me
But ma 'am , there is nothing here apart from old graves
I think he 's gone
Come on , I 'll take you to your car
Bastard ... !
What should I do ?
What to do ? What to do ?
Come on then ... Come on , we 'll show you
Let 's go
Who was he ?
God knows . But he had it in for me
Camera ... And then a pan up ...
Hey , Big Guy , what work do you do ?
- Looking for a job . - A job ?
Then come with us
- You can 't ... - Shut up !
It 's 2 days away
But I 'm sure you can get a job . My uncle . ..
Her uncle owns a big sawmill
- Send this timber to Jawahar . - Yes , sir
Thakur sir , Jasmin is ill again
Get away from here !
Open the door !
I 'll kill you all !
Break the door down
- Ramu , call the doctor . - Yes
Blood pressure is normal
Doctor why are you here .. . ?
What happened ?
What 's going on ?
- You don 't remember ? - What 's that , doctor ?
Nothing , dear
She doesn 't remember a thing
How long has Jasmin been like this ?
Since she was 1 0
She 's been seen by so many doctors , wise men
but to no avail
Jasmin needs psychiatric help , not physical treatment , sir
i 'm a psychiatrist
I 've treated many such cases
Send her to my clinic . I 'll have a look at her
Thanks
Thakela Guest House
Wow ! What a location ! Thakela guest house
A guest house or a haunted house ?
Whatever . We only need a room
We 'll only stay here one night
Have any room you want
We 've had no guests for years
- There are 3 problems here . - Which are ?
Wild dogs and cats get into the rooms through the bathroom
Second problem : the taps are broken in all the bathrooms
Good excuse for a sexy scene , then
And third : There are huge fans in every room
But they only work once a year
And even then , only on nights of the full moon
What a setting . We must stay here
Quiet ! The Big Boss is coming
He doesn 't like any noise . He 's a very strict man
What an intro .. . Sound ! Camera ! Action !
Cut ! What a let down
- Meet my esteemed elder brother . - Elder brother ?
For an older brother , don 't you think he 's a bit
short ?
When my brother was born , there was an earthquake in the hospital
lt scared him so much he stayed the way he was then
Fine . Show them the room
Justice Chaudhary in 8mm
Come , do come
This is his room . And this is her room
- What ? - l mean , this is madam 's room
There 's a connecting door
You can open it at night and talk whenever you want
What are you looking at ! Get out !
What does the heartbeat say ?
Ask your heart
My heart says to embrace you
No , no , no
What does the heartbeat say ?
Ask your heart
My heart says to embrace you
No , no , no
How you touched me !
God knows what has happened to me
What had to happen , that 's what happened
Whatever happened was good
Sometimes here , sometimes there
God knows where you tease me
Let us meet openly
I 'm young , you 're young
What does the heartbeat say ?
Ask your heart
My heart says to embrace you
No , no , no
Your body is full of blossoms
Your body is full of lusciousness
Why are you embracing me ?
Why are you after me ?
What I want , you want that too
Refusal on your lip , consent in your eyes
I know you
I 'll not listen to you
What does the heartbeat say ?
Ask your heart
My heart says to embrace you
No , no , no
Mr Director , your hero and heroine have left for Chandan village
When are you leaving ?
I 'll stay here for another 1 5 days
I 'll be scouting all the good locations
Your pants are ready
Here
Come in
Come in ? ...
Why ?
I just dropped the soap . Come on .. .
Make nice juicy betel
And listen , put in 2 sleeping pills
Jasmin
Yes , ma 'am . Need some gas ?
- Fill her up . - Sure . ..
Wow !
I mean ... it 's a brand new car , eh ?
Keys , ma 'am
Listen , I have a problem with the accelerator pedal
The cable was loose , that 's all
You 're a very good mechanic
I 've repaired a lot of great cars , ma 'am
Really ?
Then come to the lake behind the old villa tonight
I have something I want you to fix for me
She 's got him hooked
You 're soon to enjoy the pleasures of Chandan village
Raghu , who was that babe ?
She 's the daughter of the boss of Chandan village
She often goes wandering in the lonely woods at night
She 's looking for a man
Tonight is your lucky night . Down by the lake
What is this place you 've brought me to ?
Wow ! Great ! Such an old vintage !
The older the vintage , the stronger it gets
You drink ?
Only when it 's mixed with the pleasures of youth
I hope I won 't disappoint
Pour two glasses . Let 's make a night of it
I 'd never imagined that tonight would bring such pleasures
To a beautiful night
The night is still young
Let 's drink to what 's yet to come
The heat of your body has set this place on fire
There 's no need to wait any longer
The union of fire and gunpowder is dangerous
The fire of lust is even more dangerous
Hail Mahakal !
So ... Come in , Hemant . Make yourself at home
What a beautiful house
Of course it 's beautiful . It 's my uncle 's house
But where is he ?
Uncle ! .. . Uncle !
What 's up ?
- Aren 't you happy I 'm here ? - No , of course I am
I 'm very happy . Come along
Who 's this ?
I forgot to introduce him ... It 's Hemant
lf l 'd not met him yesterday then I might not be here today
How come ?
On the way a goon attacked her
She shouted for help . And I helped her
I am so grateful to you
Why are you standing ? Come ...
- How are you ? - Fine . What about you ?
I 'm fine
- Baba , bring the tea . - Yes , sir
What work do you do ?
He wants to talk to you about that
I have several factories
And I need a trustworthy man to look after my interests
Consider me as your own son , Thakur sir
From now on , don 't call me Thakur sir
Call me father
Uncle , where is Jasmin ?
- She 's upstairs in her room . - l 'll go say hello
Sister !
Sister
You scared me
- How are you , sister ? - Fine . How are you ?
I 'm fine . But you 've not changed . You 're just the same
Still hiding away in your room
Come
Bastard !
Damn cat ! You spilled the milk !
If I see you again , I 'll cut you up and feed the bits to the dogs !
Hey , mosquito ! Who are you ? And where have you come from ?
I 'll tell you . ..
First put the knife down . .. I 've wet myself
You see ...
The king of horror and suspense
- You 've heard the name Hitchcock ? - Yes
I 'm a distant relative of his
What are you staring at ?
I 'm checking her from every angle
I see great potential in her
She can be India 's top heroine . Top heroine !
How many films have you made ?
Many , many ...
But none of them released in India
All released overseas
My films are all super hits overseas . In Japan , for example ...
Real horror movies ?
What are you saying , man ?
Before every show an ambulance is parked outside the theatre
Just in case someone gets too scared
ln every show at least 1 50 people run out of the theatre
To change their pants
But today you gave me diarrhoea
- Where 's the bathroom ? - Upstairs
Who is it ?
We asked the villagers . But they don 't know him
He has been brutally murdered
- Arrange for the post mortem . - Okay , sir
I 'm telling the truth , sir
They found a body by the lake
The police are there
Nobody in the village knows who he is
But I know who he is
You won 't like it , Thakur sir
Jasmin was with him yesterday down by the lake
Rubbish , Raghu !
But I saw it with my own eyes , Thakur sir
Jasmin ...
Where is she ?
Beloved ... my beloved
From that world to this world , I came in search of you
Beloved ... where are you ?
Where are you ? Where are you ? Where are you ?
The flame is burning . Where is the lover ?
The heart is here . Where is the crazy one ?
Beloved ... where are you ?
Where are you ? Where are you ? Where are you ?
So , baby . .. Do you want a lift ?
I said do you want a ride ?
- Where are you going ? - Where you are going
I mean , wherever you want to go , I 'll drop you there
My clothes are wet
That 's just fine by me
I can wash the car out later . Don 't worry about it
Get in . Have a seat
Sir , another stranger 's corpse has been found in the same spot
ln a car
There were wounds on the corpse
The eyes were staring in fright
He had been savagely slaughtered
Did they find out who did it ?
They have no suspect yet , sir
But besides the corpse
was a handkerchief drenched with blood
lt has your family 's symbol
Sir , your daughter is linked with these deaths
Papa . What is it ?
Were you in the woods yesterday ?
Why ?
I just was ...
- You met a stranger there . - Stranger ?
You asked for a ride
And today they found his body covered with blood
Blood ... ? But , daddy ...
The man you went with yesterday
I didn 't go with anyone
You 're lying !
I 'm not lying , papa ! I 'm telling the truth
I didn 't go with anybody
Then why was your handkerchief found beside the body ?
I don 't know
I didn 't meet any man
I didn 't get in any car
l don 't know who killed him !
I don 't know why my handkerchief was found there !
Believe me , papa !
Please believe me
My dear .. .
I know you 're as pure and innocent as I think
But . ..
We can 't stop people talking
Why do you shut yourself away ?
Why do you wander the lonely woods at night ?
What do you do out there ?
Tell me , dear
I 'll do what I want . Just leave me alone
Producer sir , try to understand my helplessness
I have a scheduling problem
Each producer gets one hour from me every day
What !
You want to make a Bhojpuri horror movie ! But ...
Hello ... Director sir
Hello ... Producer sir
Forgive me
Raghu , I 've told you to keep that cat out of here
She 's Baba 's pet , sir
Or else I would long since
have poisoned her milk
Uncle , I 'll stay with Jasmin tonight
No , dear . You 'll sleep in your room
Let her stay with me , dad
We 've been apart such a long time
Nakita
Nakita , wake up
Who is it ?
What is it , Sahila ? What 's wrong ?
Hemant .. in there ... It 's ... Jasmin
- Where 's Jasmin ? - She 's not in her bed
Outside in the balcony
Her face ...
lt 's not Jasmin . It 's someone else
- Come . - No ...
Feels like she 's burning up
You damned creature !
You 've made my life a hell !
What is it ?
Why were you screaming ?
There 's blood on your face
lt 's that damned cat 's fault
I was sleeping here . It attacked me
- lt wants to kill me ! - Then you must kill it first
He 'll never be able to catch it
Why can 't he catch it ?
Come ...
Listen to me
- Get a sack with a stick in it - Stick . ..
To hold the sack open
Put some fish inside it
The cat smells it and goes in
Then , pull the stick away to close the sack
- And with the stick ... - Kill the cat !
You look like an idiot . But you 're a real director
And you 're not even an extra
Come , in my dear
I don 't know why he sent me to you
He worries over nothing
There 's nothing wrong with me , doctor
I know that , my dear
But to put his mind at ease I 'll do some tests
I 'll ask some questions . And you 'll answer me
OK , doctor
Let your limbs feel loose
Just clear your mind of any worries
And just do what I say
Now look closely at this
Just concentrate on it
Keep looking at it . Keep looking at it ...
Now your eyelids are becoming heavy
Now you 're feeling sleepy
Sleepy ...
Now you 're sleeping ... Sleeping
Now you 're asleep
Jasmin , we 're going back into the past .. .
Some years ago ...
No . .. ! No ... !
Get me out of here !
Get me out of here
Uncle ! .. . Uncle , save me !
Jasmin ...
Where are you ?
In the dark forest
I 'm not Jasmin ! I 'm not Jasmin !
I 'll kill them ! I 'll kill them all !
I 'll kill Thakur Mahindra Pratap and all his family !
I 'll kill them all !
lmpossible ! I don 't believe it !
I 've recorded her voice too
But the voice is not Jasmin 's
lt 's someone else
It seems like someone else is speaking from inside her
I 'm not Jasmin ! I 'm not Jasmin !
I 'll kill them ! I 'll kill them all !
I 'll kill Thakur Mahindra Pratap and all his family !
I 'll kill them all !
Was there any incident in her childhood that had a deep affect on her ?
When Jasmin was 1 0 years old ...
My brother Sameer took her back to her school in the city
That night ... God knows what happened
Sameer died out there in the lonely forest
When my child returned from that terrible place ...
.. .she wasn 't Jasmin
Don 't lose hope , please . I 'll cure your daughter
And I 'm sure she 'll get well
Stay here for a few days ...
lt 'll put me at ease
I 'll stay here until Jasmin has her next attack
What 's up , Raghu ? Why are you shouting ?
In this mirror ...
.. .l saw a face
A hideous witch
And when I turned round
there was no-one
There 's nothing wrong with you . Just stop smoking
I want to give up
But it won 't give me up
And then the heroine 's father turned into a dog
Milk
- Put it in this skull . - Skull ?
When I drink milk from this skull ...
. .. new ideas jump into my head like a frog
I was just thinking about you
- About me ? - Yes
I want to give you a big part
Look , I know nothing about acting ...
Only that I don 't like it
Just try it once , then you 'll get used to it
And then gradually , you 'll get to like it
You have the spark in you . A director like me can see that
What 's going on ?
I killed her
- Oh my God ! - You killed the cat ?
You 'll be reborn as a dog
Shhh ! Don 't say that
- Now what will you do - Bury her behind the house
Hitchcock will find you the perfect location for it
Now where shall we dig ?
Hey ! Hey ! come on .. . There 's digging to do
I killed her
What next ? Killing the cat ?
Beloved ... my beloved
From that world to this world , I came in search of you
Beloved ... where are you ?
Where are you ? Where are you ? Where are you ?
For so long l 've been hungry for love
Come and satisfy my hunger tonight
Beloved ... where are you ?
Where are you ? Where are you ? Where are you ?
Beloved ... my beloved
From that world to this world , I came in search of you
Beloved ... where are you ?
Where are you ? Where are you ? Where are you ?
Hemant ... what are you thinking about ?
Sahila . .. I was thinking about Jasmin
Whenever I look in her eyes ... something happens to me
There ...
That cat 's voice
The dead cat 's alive ?
No , no . It 's not that cat ...
lt must be that cat 's ghost . Ghost ! Ghost !
It 's only 1 1 o 'clock . What 's all the fuss about ?
- Cat .. . - Cat ?
I heard that damn cat 's voice
What are you saying , man ? That cat is dead
Cat !
If the cat 's dead , then what was that ?
I reckon that cat didn 't die
How come ?
I myself saw you bury that cat six foot under
Come on , let 's dig it up
No , you go and do it
You 're afraid of a cat ? I 'll do the digging
You know , you look like a butcher
Yet you 're afraid of a dead cat
Now just watch . I 'll dig the grave .. .
And show you the white bones of a black cat
See that tire ? This is where we dug
1 .. . 2 ... 3 ... 4 ... 5 ... 6 ... 7 ... Eyyyyyy ... ..
Something 's pulling me ! Something 's pulling !
What 's going on ?
He went to dig up a cat and became a dog
Look at his face . It 's hideous
That 's it ...
I 'm never making a horror film as long as I live
What 's that ? Are you crazy ?
No , sir , I 'm not crazy . You must believe what I say
- You are deluded , doctor . - lt 's the truth , I tell you
I saw it with my own eyes . Her face changed
lt wasn 't human , it was a monster 's face
- This is impossible . - You are impossible , sir
i 'm warning you about a terrible danger
Your daughter , she ... She will bring death to you all
She will destroy everyone in this house , including you
You 're insane , doctor . You 've lost your mind
Do you expect a father to believe this of his own child ?
What child ? Your daughter died years ago
Look carefully
Behind the mask of her innocent face lurks an evil witch
What 's up , doc ? You still here ?
You must all leave now
There 's evil here . Death is waiting for you all
Listen to me . And you too should leave this house
But doctor , death can happen anywhere
All right then . Stay here and wait for death
Some doctor ... He didn 't do a lot of good
Kill them all !
I 'll kill them all !
Yes , Raghu ?
What 's the bad news today ?
The Doctor ... Has left the house
He wanted to run away from death
But he didn 't know that death was waiting for him out there
I 'll not go back there
I 'll sleep here tonight
I won 't go back there
Who could that be so late at night ?
Who is it ? Who 's there ?
The bodies are piling up
First the doctor who came to cure them went crazy
Slept under a moving truck
After that , Kaliya 's brother Raghu
Got sliced up in the factory
Why on earth should he put his hand in the machine ?
I think that Baba is behind all this
How can you say that ? Baba ...
Let him speak
So ... ?
I 've often see Baba going out after midnight
The very first time I saw that man 's ugly mug ...
. .. I knew that he would be the villain of this tale
Tonight I will keep an eye on Baba
I want to know where he goes in the middle of the night
OK , Sahila , let 's go
Where did he go ?
I think he went that way
Hemant !
Hail Mahakal !
Stop !
Otherwise I 'll cut her into pieces
Let go of him . Please let go of him
I am begging you to stop
Let go of him !
For God 's sake , let go of him
Hail Mahakal !
Now you can start hurting him again
You bastard . You scum !
At last we see your true colours
You are not human
You are a devil !
I am not a devil
- But I worship the devil . - You are a traitor !
Disguised as a servant , you have betrayed everybody
I was disguised as a servant to plan revenge ...
.. .against Thakur Mahendra Pratap and his family
Revenge ! Revenge for what ?
Papa ... It can 't be ...
She is your daughter !
Sahila ?
is it really you ?
My daughter ... ?
Papa ! is it really you , papa ?
- Papa ! - My child ...
You bastard . You scum
You have trapped me here all these years
Now you threaten these innocent kids
What is it you want .. . ?
Why have tormented me and kept me alive all these years ?
Today is once again the same dark moonless night
... for which I have waited so many years
Try to remember it , Thakur
Fifteen years ago today you killed my dark mistress Nakita
And tonight I will sacrifice your daughter Jasmin
And Nakita will be incarnated in the flesh once again
You killed Nakita
And now Nakita will kill you
Nakita will emerge from the dark past
And she will triumph over death forever
Jasmin ...
Now you are under my control
You will do only what I command you to do
Tonight I will sacrifice you
And Nakita will be reborn once again
- Why are you here ? - l 'm a horror film director
We get everywhere
You were in a carriage . I followed on a bike
A horse carriage , followed by a jeep ...
Followed by a bike And me on the bike
Quietly , man ! They might hear us
- Hitchcock ! - Hitchcock always gets it right
Behind you !
People who move ahead never look round
OK , sweetie . Know what I mean ?
Hey ! What 's going on back there ?
Someone 's strangling me
I don 't like this . What 's going on ?
Put me down !
You hit me ! You hit me !
I 'll show you ... No !
Might get arrested
Hey ! Please save me
The big guy 's after me
I don 't know what he wants . But it looks bad
I 've found the keys
Father , today the light has come back into your life
Sameer !
My brother !
You 're really alive ?
Where ... Where have you been all these years
I thought you 'd gone and left me alone here
Maybe this was the Almighty 's wish
But where have you been all these years ?
Baba told me . ..
That bastard was the one who locked him up
Baba was really our enemy
He tried to ruin our whole family
He 's the one who turned Jasmin into an evil witch ...
That 's your Baba !
He 's a devil worshipper , a black magician
He 's used that black magic on Jasmin
That 's why she haunts those lonely woods
Yes , brother !
He cut Jasmin 's hair and dress and made a doll out of it
And he buried that doll in Nakita 's grave
We must remove that doll from Nakita 's grave
Or Nakita 's evil soul will never let go of Jasmin 's body
But where is Jasmin ?
Try her room
Jasmin 's not here
She 's not there either
Where 's Baba gone ?
He 's taken Jasmin back to the dark woods
Tonight will be a moonless night
Tonight , in front of his evil God . ..
... he will sacrifice Jasmin
And then Nakita will live again
Save my daughter , Sameer !
- Save my daughter ! - Don 't worry , father !
I will save Jasmin
Your death will bring about Nakita 's rebirth
You must enter that burning cave
Your body will be burned to ashes
And Nakita 's soul will enter her own body once again
Jasmin !
Jasmin ... . ! Stay where you are !
Stop , my daughter ... Stop
So , Thakur Mahendra Pratap Singh ...
. .. at last you are here
You deceitful rat
You have destroyed my home
The black magic of Mahakal will destroy you if you oppose it
That evil magic has cursed our family
But there is a power even greater than your Mahakal
And that is God Almighty
Stop your devilish laughter !
Now prepare to meet your doom
Tonight I will destroy your citadel of evil
Seize him !
Don 't let him get away
Wait , Thakur ! Don 't make this mistake
By the power of black magic , once this bottle breaks
Nakita will leave your daughter 's body
But you will die
As soon as this bottle breaks , then you will die
I was already dead on the day you bewitched my daughter
If my death will save my daughter 's life
then I accept this death
Father !
Papa , what 's happened to you ?
Daughter , are you all right ?
Tell me , papa . What 's happened to you ?
Sahila , don 't look at her
Don 't look in her eyes !
She will kill you all !
You will all die !
The AUM must be under this statue
Hemant ! Trap her in there !
After even the blackest night can come a bright new morning
Every death is followed by the rebirth of new life and hope
Darkness is driven away
The cycle of seasons starts anew
Behind the secrets of nature lies a greater power
Almighty God ! Whose power vanquishes all evil